I just saw those things
and suddenly remembered
I think I saw you when we were kids too
You think
Earlier you were certain
Sis if you had told me earlier
how could I have misunderstood
If I had told you earlier
would you not have taken my stuff
The problem isn't whether I told you
The problem is that when you got
the old things that weren't yours
your first reaction wasn't to return them
but to cover up the signature
and claim the story was yours
I was just too scared
Scared of what
Miss Su please write
I'm sorry sis
I just wanted to help
Before you help
return other people's things first
Chairman we got the original items
The companion signature on the receipt is Su Mingyao
The backup predates the wedding
Su Yurou admitted the items
came from Su Mingyao's box of old things
Verify them according to procedure
Understood
Is Fu Chenzhou present
Yes
The Chairman wants a word with you